// Should store an array of objects, with each object a set of question properties and values, which we can reference. 

let QUESTIONS = [
    {
        question: "Who is Zelda?",
        answers: [
            "The young hero dressed in green.",
            "The Princess of Hyrule.",
            "The fairy queen.",
            "The evil demon king."],
        correct: "The Princess of Hyrule."
    }, 
    {
        question: "When was Ocarina of Time originally released?",
        answers: [
            "October, 1993.",
            "December, 1999.",
            "November, 1998.",
            "December, 2003."],
        correct: "November, 1998."
    },
    {
        question: "What console was the title released on?",
        answers: [
            "Nintendo 64.",
            "playstaion.",
            "Super Nintendo.",
            "Dreamcast."],
        correct: "Nintendo 64."
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the main character?",
        answers: [
            "Zelda.",
            "Saori.",
            "Epona.",
            "Link."
        ],
        correct: "Link."
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of hero's fairy?",
        answers: [
            "Navi.",
            "Epona.",
            "Theo.",
            "Malta."
        ],
        correct: "Navi."
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of ther hero's horse?",
        answers: [
            "Saria",
            "Ted",
            "Epona",
            "Malon"
        ],
        correct: "Epona."
    },
    {
        question: "What is the blade weilded by the hero?",
        answers: [
            "Eternity's Edge",
            "The Sword of Time",
            "Demon's Bane",
            "The Master Blade"
        ],
        correct: "The Master Blade"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the main villain?",
        answers: [
            "Ganondorf",
            "The Great Fairy",
            "Pierre",
            "Kaepora Gaebora"
        ],
        correct: "Ganondorf"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Sheik?",
        answers: [
            "The Prince of Hyrule",
            "The Keeper of Time",
            "Princess Zelda",
            "King Ganondorf's son"
        ],
        correct: "Princess Zelda"
    },
    {
        question: "What happens when you attack the chickens?",
        answers: [
            "They lay eggs",
            "They drop chicken sticks",
            "They kill you",
            "You gain the powers of a chicken for 2 minutes"
        ],
        correct: "They kill you"
    }
]